Guide to the New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NYCOSH) Records WAG.029
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Unprocessed Material, 1971-2011; 545012
  - Box 63, 1981-2011; cuid8011; 545064
    This box contains a mockup of a poster for the NYCOSH-sponsored Right to Know Conference in 1981, a poster for the centennial commemoration of the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory fire, and three poster advertisements regarding workers' compensation for 9/11 responders (one in Spanish). There are also several federal, state, and local government proclamations recognizing Workers Memorial Days and Teen Worker Safety Month, as well as a "VDT Safety Now!" button and an informational booklet created by the New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO on Public Employees Safety and Health (PESH)Act/OSHA standards.
  - NYCOSH film, "Worker to Worker", 1987; cuid8013 (Reel 1)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    16mm film, 1200 ft.
  - NYCOSH film, "Can't Take No More", undated; cuid8014 (Reel 2, Reel cuid8014_1, Reel 3)
    16mm film, 2400 ft., 2 reels.
- Series IV: Archived Website, Apr 16, 2009-ongoing; cuid8012; 547021
  New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NYCOSH), founded in 1980, is a non-profit coalition of 200 local unions and more than 400 individual workers, physicians, lawyers and other health and safety activists dedicated to the right of worker safety on the job. NYCOSH operates throughout New York City, Long Island and the Lower Hudson Valley. The website gives information and assistance for those injured on the job and other training and safety resources.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.